Looks like things in the AI space are
about to get a lot more crazier as the
Google Deep Mind team has been dropping
hints about a potential Gemini 3.0
release next week. And according to
sources that I'm tapped in with, the big
date could be October 9th. Now, what
makes this super exciting is the waves
of leaks, sneak peeks, as well as
whisperers suggested not just one, but
two models. The Gemini 3.0 Flash as well
as the Gemini 3.0 Note Pro. Both are
rumored to be state-of-the-art and many
are calling them to be the best AI
models ever released. And the best part
is you can actually access them today.
Just take a look at this example where
someone prompted the Gemini 3.0 Pro to
generate a SAS landing page from
scratch. And the results were insane. It
pumped out nearly 2,300 lines of code in
seconds. And it built a fullon landing
page. and it absolutely beat Zenith in
web designing and the output is just
truly stunning cuz it looks like a real
web page. Here is another example of a
Twitter clone that was fully generated
using the Gemini 3.0 and this is
probably the best output generation of a
Twitter clone that I have seen from a
model. This is something that it had
coded up fully on its own and you can
see that it looks exactly like Twitter.
And I know you may be wondering how are
people actually getting generations with
the Gemini 3.0. Well, the thing is the
Google team has been introducing a new
AB testing for this model where it's a
feature that they rolled out within
Google AI Studio where you need to just
simply select the Gemini 2.5 Pro. And
this lets the user actually compare
between model outputs if they're
actually selected. So in this case you
can say something like create me a SAS
landing page and then you can send in
the prompt and there is a chance that
this particular prompt will be sent in
to two different uh models and that is
where you can basically visualize the AB
testing where Google is testing the
performance of the Gemini 3.0 0 versus
the Gemini 2.5 Pro. And you'll get to
see which model did a better job. And
you can see right now I didn't actually
get it. So if you are looking to get the
response from the Gemini 3.0 Pro, just
simply go ahead and keep refreshing it
and sending in that same prompt to see
if you can maybe get the AB testing that
gets you access to the Gemini 3.0. Now,
thanks to this developer on Twitter, I
was able to make this video. So, I
highly recommend that you give him a
follow because he was able to actually
give me some insights on this new AB
testing. So, I highly recommend that you
follow him because he's always posting a
lot of insights on the new AI news that
has been dropping over the past couple
of months. Before we get started, I just
want to mention that you should
definitely go ahead and subscribe to the
World of AI newsletter. I'm constantly
posting different newsletters on a
weekly basis. So this is where you can
easily get up-to-date knowledge about
what is happening in the AI space. So
definitely go ahead and subscribe as
this is completely for free. Now
personally I believe that Google is
going to be winning hard with this
release and it's because this model is
insanely smart with the generations I'm
about to showcase you. I'll be running
more prompts in a couple of different
videos as well, but this is truly insane
in terms of its coding performance. I
believe that it's going to top the ARC
AGI. It's going to be able to achieve
parody with human experts on GDP evolves
and it can even handle a 100h hour task
streak with different sorts of
benchmarks. Now, from my current test,
this thing is super fast and insanely to
the point. I honestly think it's going
to be a beast inside Gemini CLI for
rapid efficient coding. And this is just
speculation, but I believe we might see
this new Gemini 3.0 model having a 2
million context window. But this is a
thread of different videos that I'll be
showcasing and highlighting which
showcases its creativity, world
knowledge, coding skill, and scientific
reasoning. Here is where someone had
actually built a solar system simulation
where it was requested to build a
real-time solar system from scratch
which generated physics-based orbital
mechanics scaling and interactive
frontends to showcase all these
visualizations. And you can see that
this is something that is insanely
qualitative in comparison to other
models. When you prompt this exact
prompt with something like the Claude
4.5, you wouldn't get this exceptional
generation. This is the only model that
was capable of generating this
qualitative output with 2,000 plus lines
of code of a working render. It's
front-end designing skills are
absolutely amazing, too, cuz you can see
that it was able to create a Mac OSbased
browser operator with SVG code. It also
does pretty good as well. You can see
that it created a pretty good looking
Xbox and PS5 controller in SVG, which
most models tend to actually fail at
doing. So, this is what I mean by AB
testing. Whenever you send in a prompt
like create me a SAS landing page,
you'll see these two different cards pop
up. And essentially, it's testing out
two different models. And one of them is
actually the Gemini 3.0 Pro. So once it
has finished generating, you're going to
be able to actually get the code from it
and you'll be able to visualize what it
actually generated. Nephi, if you're
looking to get the AB testing enabled,
it's going to take approximately 10 to
35 prompts to actually get that. And you
might not even get the Gemini 3.0 cuz in
certain cases, they test other models in
that particular generation. So just keep
that in mind. And there we go. This is
our SAS landing page that it had
generated. Now, it looks absolutely
amazing cuz it is feature-p packed with
a lot of different things that you
wouldn't see in a typical AI SAS landing
page. This was all fully coded out with
the Gemini 3.0. And you can see there's
various components that have been added.
There's animations, the pricing
structure, but the formatting is one
thing that it needs a bit of work on,
which is why maybe they're testing it
out within Google AI Studio so that they
can refine it a bit further before their
actual release. But overall, I'm pretty
impressed with its generation for this
SAS landing page. This was an app that I
had generated, which is a time
management app in a single shot. And to
be honest, this one doesn't look too
extraordinary. It looks pretty simple
and something that most models can
actually generate. But I guess in a
single shot, it did a great job in
generating this. If you like this video
and would love to support the channel,
you can consider donating to my channel
through the super thanks option below.
Or you can consider joining our private
Discord where you can access multiple
subscriptions to different AI tools for
free on a monthly basis, plus daily AI
news and exclusive content, plus a lot
more. Overall, that's basically it,
guys, for today's video on this new
sneak peek on the Gemini 3.0. You can
just see from this test over here,
there's 23k tokens used for this
generation. And I've been just using it
constantly throughout the day to see
what I can generate with the Gemini 3.0.
And it's truly remarkable. Now, I highly
recommend that you try this out, the AB
testing method to access the Gemini 3.0,
but obviously you will be able to access
it next week, hopefully on the 9th. But
that's basically it, guys. Thank you
guys so much for watching. I hope you
enjoyed today's video and got some sort
of value. Make sure you subscribe to
this developer who has been giving me a
lot of tips on the AB testing. Make sure
you go ahead and subscribe to the second
channel. Join our newsletter. Join our
private Discord. Follow me on Twitter.
And lastly, make sure you guys
subscribe, turn on notification bell,
like this video, and please take a look
at our previous videos cuz there is a
lot of content that you'll truly benefit
from. But with that thought, guys, thank
you guys so much for watching. I really
really appreciate it guys if you guys
can go ahead and comment what you would
like to see in the next couple of
videos. But that's basically it guys.
Thank you so much for watching and I'll
see you guys fairly soon. He suffers.